Ethan@Your room is very girly.
Emily@What are you talking about?
Ethan@Well... it smells nice.
Ethan@You're reading books too?
Emily@Yes, I am.
Ethan@I really like the author of this book.
Emily@I know.
Ethan@You know?
Ethan@What other books do you read?
Ethan@What's wrong?
Emily@Nothing.
Ethan@You keep a handwritten diary?
Ethan@Aren't many people forgetting how to write characters these days?
Emily@Yeah, that's true.
Ethan@Let me take a look.
Emily@We don't need this for now.
Emily@It's just some usual habits.
Ethan@How mysterious.
Ethan@So...
Ethan@So, what are you going to do later?
Emily@Later... I don't have any plans.
Ethan@Then...
Ethan@How about we go for afternoon tea or something like that?
Emily@Sure, that sounds good.
Ethan@What flavor of cake do you like?
Ethan@What's that?
Emily@Ethan...
Emily@That's not okay.
Ethan@A-Actually...
Ethan@I also... ...
Ethan@No, that's not right.
Ethan@I, I, I wasn't sure before.
Ethan@Do, do you like me too?
Ethan@Anyway, thank you.
Ethan@Thank you for liking me too.
Ethan@I think it's about time.
Ethan@I, I should go now.
Ethan@Let's meet again next time.
Emily@Wait a moment.
Emily@Can you stay with me a little longer?
Emily@Is that okay?